{
    "subject": "Charles_Emmanuel_III_of_Sardinia",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Countess_Palatine_Anne_Christine_of_Sulzbach",
    "human_readable": "Charles Emmanuel III of Sardinia is married to Countess Palatine Anne Christine of Sulzbach.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.973242998123169,
            "question": "Was Charles Emmanuel III of Sardinia married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9727826118469238,
            "question": "Who was Charles Emmanuel III of Sardinia married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8975011110305786,
            "question": "Who is Countess Palatine Anne Christine of Sulzbach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8773599863052368,
            "question": "What is the connection between Countess Palatine Anne Christine and Charles Emmanuel III?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7931405305862427,
            "question": "What was the name of Charles Emmanuel III's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6313215494155884,
            "question": "What was the name of Countess Palatine Anne Christine's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6161032319068909,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the family background of Countess Palatine Anne Christine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5661115646362305,
            "question": "To which royal family did Charles Emmanuel III belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3684925138950348,
            "question": "Who was the king of Sardinia during this time period?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16391818225383759,
            "question": "Where might we find more information about this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles Emmanuel III of Sardinia is married to Countess Palatine Anne Christine of Sulzbach.",
            "html": "yago_21708_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the king of Sardinia during this time period?",
            "html": "yago_21708_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which royal family did Charles Emmanuel III belong?",
            "html": "yago_21708_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the family background of Countess Palatine Anne Christine?",
            "html": "yago_21708_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21708_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21708/re-ranker-msmarco/54.txt, it is stated that Anne Christine of Sulzbach was married to Charles Emmanuel, Prince of Piedmont.\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21708/re-ranker-msmarco/120.txt, it is also confirmed that Countess Palatine Anne Christine of Sulzbach was married to Charles Emmanuel, Prince of Piedmont.\n* There is no mention in the documents of Charles Emmanuel III being a different person than Charles Emmanuel, Prince of Piedmont.\n\nTherefore, based on the information provided, I conclude that:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Charles Emmanuel III of Sardinia is married to Countess Palatine Anne Christine of Sulzbach.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention their marriage and give details about each other's backgrounds."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}